嘿      嘿 等我一下
Hey.         Hey. Hold on a second.
厉害 厉害
Nice. Nice.
有东西要给你      这是什么
Hey, I got you something for you.        What's this?
812块钱
Eight hundred and twelve bucks.
我不知道老鸨怎么跟你说的
I don't know what Big Leon told you.
跟我过夜 要一千大洋才够
But it's an even thousand if you want me for the whole night.
这是在干嘛啊      我现在开始赚钱了
What is this for?         Well, I'm making money now.
这是还你拍大头照的钱 电费
And this is paying you back for headshots, electric bills,
以及无数披萨的钱等等
and so many slices of pizza I can't even count.
我爱你 老兄      那谢啦 老兄
I love you, man.       Well thanks. man.
这下子我有钱买个小马了
Now I can get my pony.
我还有个小礼物要送给你 感谢你永远支持我
Hey. This is a little extra something for, you know, always being there for me.
哇 我不晓得该说什么才好
Wow, I don't know what to say.
你觉得怎样      我不知道
What do you say?         I don't know.
这是一条手链
It's a bracelet.
可不是吗 还刻了字 快看看
Isn't it? It's engraved too. Check it out.
送给我的好哥们儿
"To my best bud"
谢了 好哥们儿
Thanks, best bud.
戴上吧     现在吗
Put it on.         Oh. Now?
不 这么美的东西 应该留到特殊的场合再戴
No, no. I think something this nice should be saved for a special occasion.
不 美就美在这儿 它配什么都好看
Oh, no no, that's the beauty part. It goes with everything.
戴上这个 你就可以风风光光地出门
You put this on, you're good to go.
哦 哇
Oh, man!
这手链真是太配你了
You are so wearing that bracelet!
可不是嘛
I so am!
知道这种东东 会为你的性生活带来什么好处吗
You have any idea what this'll do for your sex life?
刚开始时可能会让我慢半拍
It'll probably slow it down at first.
等我习惯这种重量之后 我就会重振雄风了
But once I'm used to the extra weight, I'll be back on track.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光收藏版 第02季 第14集
高中舞会录影带 The One With the Prom Video
字幕编辑：海盗美剧 小龟快快跑
调校制作：海盗美剧 寒 枫
看起来都很棒      太好了
Well, this all looks good.         Great.
如果我想找人问问你过去的工作表现呢
And if I wanna call for a reference on your last job.
就在这下面 看 经理是钱德宾
Oh, that's there on the bottom. See, the manager, Chandler Bing?
好的
All right.
我们就来看看 你本人有没有那么好
Let's see if you're as good in person as you are on paper.
给我做个沙拉
Make me a salad.
沙拉吗 我可以做难度更高的东西
A salad? Really I, I could do something a little more complicated if you like.
不 沙拉就可以了
No, just the salad will be fine.
没问题
You got it.
好 我要你一边做一边告诉我你在做什么
Now I want you to tell me what you're doing while you're doing it.
好的 我在撕莴苣
All right. Well, I'm tearing the lettuce.
莴苣很脏吗
Uhhuh. Is it dirty?
不 放心好了 我会清洗的
Oh, no, no, don't worry. I'm gonna wash it.
不要 我喜欢脏脏的
Don't. I like it dirty.
悉听尊便了
That's your call.
你接下来要做什么呢
So, uh, what are you going to do next?
我想 我接下来要切蕃茄了
Well, I thought that I would cut up the tomatos.
蕃茄坚硬吗
Are they firm?
还可以
They're alright.
你确定没有变坏吗
You sure they haven't gone bad?
你确定没有非常非常坏吗
You sure they're not very very bad?
没坏 都还可以啦
No, really, they're okay.
你会很温柔的切开吗
You gonna slice them up real nice?
其实 我想切成细丝
Actually, I was gonna do them jullienne.
我不干了
I'm out of here!
喂
Hello?
瑞秋现在不在 要我留口信吗
No, Rachel's not here right now, can I take a message?
是哪个凯西
All right. And how do we spell Casey?
是"凯西出击" 还是 "凯希阳光合唱团"
Is it like "at the bat" or "and The Sunshine Band'?
好 再见
Okay, byebye.
嘿 这个凯西是谁啊
Hey, who's this Casey?
她看电影认识的人
Some guy she met at the movies.
真的 他找她干嘛
Oh really? What uh, what does he want with her?
我猜 他想跟她跳点小舞
I'm guessing he wants to do a little dance.
嘿咻一下
You know, make a little love.
差不多今晚就把她解决掉
Well, pretty much get down tonight.
我不晓得 我不
I don't know. I don't...
我不懂 两个月前 我跟瑞秋只差这么一点点了
I don't get it! I mean, two wo months ago, Rachel and I werel like this close.
现在我却在帮一个她看电影时遇到的家伙留话
Right now, what? I'm taking messages from guys she, she meets at the movies?
应该这个凯西帮我留言 或是
I mean this, this Casey should be taking down my messages, you know? Or or...
瑞秋应该和我在一起
Rachel and I should be together.
然后我们就需要留言服务
And we should get some kind of message service.
耐心点吧 会有那么一天的
Hang in there. It's gonna happen.
这你怎么知道
Okay, now how do you know that?
因为她是你的龙虾
Because she's your lobster.
哦 她有些想法想要表达
Oh, she's going somewhere.
龙虾一旦相爱 就会白头偕老 这是常识
C'mon you guys. It's a known fact that lobsters fall in love and mate for life.
你可以亲眼目睹 年老的龙虾夫妇在水缸里漫步
You know what? You can actually see old lobster couples walking around their tank,
钳子牵着钳子 就像这样
you know, holding claws, like...
觉得好一点了吗
Hey, you feeling better?
我想洗到第五次 就可以把面试的记忆冲掉了
Yeah. I think that fifth shower actually got the interview off me.
那你还有其他的可能吗
So do you have any other possibilities?
当然有 我有可能付不起房租
Oh yeah, well there's the possibility that I won't make rent.
摩妮卡 你有需要的话 我可以借你钱
Monica, if you want, I can lend you money.
不要 万一我无法立刻还你钱
No no no. If I couldn't pay you back right away
那每次看到你 我就会内疚紧张
then I'd feel guilty and tense every time I saw you.
那好吧 那你为什么不直接找老爸老妈借
Oh, okay, well, then why don't you borrow it from Mom and Dad?
反正在他们面前 你已经非常内疚紧张了
You feel guilty and tense around them already.
还不如趁机会跟他们刮点钱
You might as well make some money off of them.
说的有道理      喔
The man's got a point.         Ohh.
那闪闪发亮的是什么东东
What is that sparkly thing?
这玩意儿是
That thing it's a...
对 是有点俗气
Yeah, it's a little flashy.
不会 不会
No, no.
对道上的兄弟来说不算太俗
It's not flashy, not for a goodfella.
老兄 这玩意儿真显眼
Man, man that is sharp.
你一定花了不少银子吧
It must have cost you quite a few debloons.
嗨      嗨
Hi.         Hi.
亲爱的      这是什么
Hi, darling.        So what's this?
你的一些旧东西
Some of your old stuff.
亲爱的 我们要给你一个惊喜
Well, sweetie, we have a surprise for you.
我们把你的房间 变成健身房了
We're turning your room into a gym.
哇 真是没想到
Wow, that is a surprise!
容我问一下 干嘛不用罗斯的房间
Just one little question. Why not Ross room?
我们讨论过了
Gosh, we talked about that.
可是他有太多科学类的奖杯 奖状 奖章之类的
but your brother had so many science trophies and plaques and merit badges.
我们不想去惊动它们
Well, we didn't want to disturb them.
老天也不准
God forbid!
哦    嗨
Ohh.         Hi.
嗨 瑞秋 我们很遗憾听到 你的父母分手了
Hi, Rachel. Oh, we were so sorry to hear about your parents splitting up, dear.
他们只是分居而已
Oh, well, you know, they're just separated.
谁知道呢 看看吧
So, you know, never know, we'll see.
老实说 我们一点也不惊讶
I can't say any of us were surprised.
从我们认识他们开始 他们就一直很不快乐
Your parents have been unhappy ever since we've known them.
特别是在夏威夷那件事之后
Especially after that incident in Hawaii.
什么事情
What incident?
不对 不对 我一定是记错人了
No, no, no, I must be thinking of someone else.
搞不好是我自己
Maybe me!
你不是有衣服要叠吗
Don't you have some folding to do?
去叠吧 亲爱的 忙你的去吧
Go fold, dear. Fold. You fold.
要续杯吗      我不要了 谢谢
Do you want a refill?         No. I'm all right, thanks.
好吧 等我一下下 我要学得逼真一点
Okay. You gotta give me a second, I wanna get this just right.
兄弟 十一点钟方向 无敌辣妹一直在看你
Dude, eleven o'clock, totally hot babe checking you out.
感觉很不错
That was really good.
我想我可以去变性了
I think I'm ready for my penis now.
我知道你在想什么 温蒂汉堡创办人 大卫汤玛斯
I know what you're thinking. Dave Thomas, founder of Wendys.
我是盖儿      钱德
I'm Gail.         Chandler.
我真得走了 很高兴见到你
I... I really have to be somewhere, but it was nice meeting you.
什么
What?
这可真是妙不可言 他大可以送我一台录影机
Oh, this is excellent! You know he coulda gotten me a VCR.
可以给我一套高尔夫球杆
He coulda gotten me a set of golf clubs.
可他却偏偏给我弄了个 吓走女人的东西
But no! He has to get me the "woman repeller"!
破烂堆里最恶心的玩意儿
The eyesore from the Liberace house of crap!
也没差到那个程度啦
It's not that bad.
是啊 你说得倒轻巧
Oh, yeah, easy for you to say.
你又不用戴着 连T先生都不要的东西到处走
You don't have to walk around sporting some reject from the Mr. T collection.
钱德 钱德
Chandler. Chandler.
我同情那些戴着我的珠宝的傻瓜 我真的同情
"I pity the fool that puts on my jewelry! I do! I do!
我同情那些戴着 嗨
I pity that fool... Ay.
嘿 老兄 我们刚刚在玩模仿秀
Hey, man! We were just doing some impressions over here.
你来学 马塞尔马尔索(法国哑剧艺术家)
Do your Marcel Marceau.
其实演得不错
That's actually good.
你看看那家伙
Would you look at that guy?
他们聊多久了
I mean how long has he been talking to her?
滚开 臭家伙 她是服务生又不是艺妓
It's like, back off, buddy! She's a waitress, not a geisha.
我觉得她很愉快
I think she's okay.
你看看 她都推开他了 他还死不走
Look at that! See how she's pushing him away and he won't budge?
我得采取行动才行
Alright, I'm gonna do something..
我们可以在山上租间木屋 滑进滑出的 很棒
We'll get a condo right on the mountain. Ski in, ski out,it's great.
打扰一下 你是瑞秋吗
Excuse me? Are you Rachel?
什么
What?
我是罗斯盖勒
Ross Geller.
老天 你在广告上说你很美 不过 哇
God, in your ad you said you were pretty, but wow
你在干嘛
What are you, what are you doing?
哦 我的天 今天不行吗
Oh, oh my God, is this the wrong day?
真是难以置信
I don't believe it!
这件事如果成了的话 将来跟孙子们就有得吹了
well, hey, I guess if it works out we'll, we'll have something to tell the grandkids!
你会有机会的      是吗
You sure will.        Yeah?
我得走了
I've gotta go.
保重     好
Take care.        Okay.
再见了 很高兴认识你
See you later. Nice meeting you.
不客气
You're welcome.
什么      我是在救你
What?         I was saving you.
好让我结束跟一个大帅哥愉快地交谈吗
Saving me from the pleasant conversation with the interesting man?
从我刚才坐的位置看来     罗斯 听我说
From where I was...        Okay, Ross listen to me.
我不是要你救的人
I am not yours to save.
但是你是      什么
But you are.         What?
你是我的龙虾
Uh, well, you're my lobster.
你又在装玩相亲游戏吗
OK, you know what, are, are you being like, the blind date guy again?
不 你是我的龙虾
No, no, you're my lobster.
龙虾呢
See Lobsters,
在水槽里 他们变老了以后
in the tank, when they're old
会那个 他们会牵着钳子散步
they get with the... They walk around holding the claws.
在水槽里
In the tank! You know, with...
牵着钳子而且
with the holding and
菲比 帮我解释一下龙虾的事 好不好
Pheebs, you wanna help me with the lobster thing?
再做一次握的动作
Do the claws again.
瑞秋 别管龙虾了 可以吗
Rach, okay, forget the lobsters, okay?
我们来谈谈 谈谈我们如何
Let's talk. What about us?
罗斯 没有所谓的"我们" 行吗
Ross, there is no "us", okay?
可是      不 你听我说
No, but...        No! Listen to me!
我爱上你 我深受打击
I fell for you and I get clobbered.
后来你爱上我 我还是深受打击
You then fall for me and I again get somehow clobbered.
我不想再受伤了 你知道吗
I'm tired of being clobbered, you know?
这根本不值得
It's just not worth it.
但是      没有"但是"了 罗斯
Well. but...        No "but" Ross.
我们是不可能的 好吗 接受吧
We are never gonna happen, okay? Accept that.
除非什么呢
Except...Except that what?
不 不
No. No.
接受这个事实吧
Accept that.
哦
Oh.
嘿 老兄 哇 是我的好哥儿 你好吗
Hey, man! Look, it's my best bud. How you doing?
你模仿马塞尔马尔索 越来越像了
Wow. You're getting good at that Marcel Marceau thing.
我们去打球如何 就你和我 怎么样
Hey, what do you say we play some ball? You and me, huh? What do you say?
是我不好
Okay, that's my bad.
如果你不喜欢那条手链 你大可直说
If you hated the bracelet so much, Chandler, you should have just said so.
尽管我不喜欢 我还是戴着
Well, doesn't the fact that I wore the bracelet even though I hated it
这不就表示 我非常重视我们之间的友谊吗
say something about our friendship and how much it means to me?
可是你羞辱那条手链 你还取笑我
What about the fact that you insulted the bracelet and you made fun of me?
所以说 我是个王八蛋
Well that's the part where I'm a wank.
我希望你不要只注意那件事
I was hoping you wouldn't focus on that.
别这样啦 我已经向你道过一百次歉了
Come on, man! I said I was sorry a hundred times.
我保证我再也不会拿下我的
I promise, I will never take it off my...
手腕
wrist.
如果你想待在里面发脾气
But if you want to stay in there and be mad
那就待吧
you know, you just, you stay in there.
你知道吗
You know what the...
我就在这里 跪着
I am here, on my knees,
拿着这两个椅垫
holding up these couch cushions
表达我的遗憾和悔恨
as a symbol of my sorrow and regret.
就像"圣经"里的故事一样
Much like they did in biblical times.
可能你还心怀怨恨
Though you may haveth anger now.
格拉芙的屁股长得真不错
You know that Steffi Graf has quite a tushy.
我只是说说 你自己看
I'm just saying! It's right there!
嘿 大家好      嗨 亲爱的
Hey, guys.        Hi, darling.
我的孙子呢 你没把他带来
Where's my grandson? You didn't bring him?
他今天在卡萝跟苏珊那里
No. He's at Carol andSusan'stoday.
我公司也有一个女人是同性恋
A woman in my office is a lesbian.
我只是说说
I'm just saying!
杰克 快看 你看了就会笑的那个油漆广告开始了
Oh, Jack look, there's that house paint commercial that cracks you up.
你去哪里了      情感地狱
Where have you been?         Emotional hell.
他们借给你钱了吗
So, did they lend you the money yet?
还没 那是因为我还没开口
No, but that's probably 'cause I haven't asked them yet.
拜托 摩妮卡 快点
Come on, Monica, do it.
嘿 你们
Hey, you guys.
摩妮卡有事要说
Monica has some news.
很抱歉我没有早点告诉你们 可是
So listen, I'm sorry I didn't tell you this before, but
我已经没上班了 我不得不离开
I'm no longer at my job. I had to leave it.
为什么      被他们逼的
Why?         Because they made me.
你被炒鱿鱼了
You were fired?
这下子你该怎么办呢
What are you gonna do?
茱蒂 别紧张 她可是我们的小小"魔女卡"
Judy, Judy, relax, this is our little harmonica we're talking about..
我们把她教得很精
We taught her well.
你一成的薪水都会
Ten percent of your paycheck, where does it go?
存银行
In the bank.
这就对了 所以她在吃她的老本
There you go. So she dips into her savings.
存钱本来就是应急的 她不会有事的
That's what it's there for. Shes gonna be fine.
如果那些钱还不够用的话 你知道该去哪里要吧
And if you need a little extra, you know where to find it.
能变多一点吗
Anything larger back there?
真是难以置信
I can't believe it!
你能不再碎碎念了吗
Would you stop already?
就别再抱怨谷仓里的苦差事 跳到草堆里玩玩吧
Get out of the bitter barn and play in the hay.
没错 我是该跳到稻草堆里玩玩
Oh, youre right. I should play in the hay.
别忘了 我刚刚拿四百块
For about the fact that I just dropped four hundred dollars
换来一个我一开始就很讨厌的手链
to replace a bracelet that I hated to begin with.
逗我开心啊
Bring on the hay!
嘿
Hey!
我有一个能让你很开心的东西
I've got something that's gonna make you happy.
你猜阿甘找到什么东西了
Guess what Gunther found?
嘿 这下子你有两个了
Hey, now you have two!
哦 现在你有两个了哦
Oh, now you have two.
这下子我怎么办呢
What am I gonna do?
嘿
Hey.
你怎么会有两个
How come you have two?
这一个是给你的
This one's for you.
少来
Get out!
不行 少不了
No I can't.
我知道这手链对你意义有多大
No no, listen, I, I know how much this means to you.
而且我也明白 它不只是个首饰
And I also know this is about more than just jewelry.
这代表了你和我 代表我们是好哥们儿
It's about you and me and the fact that we're "best buds".
哇 这是友谊吗 我想是的
Wow. Is this friendship? I think so!
你看看 我们是手链兄弟
Check it out! We're bracelet buddies!
以后他们就会这样叫我们
That's what they'll call us!
好了 给你 你什么时候还我都可以
Okay, here you go. You can pay me back whenever you like.
你竟然有恐龙图案的支票
You have dinosaur checks?
对 你拿到钱的同时 还可以学些东西
Yeah, yeah I mean, you get your money and you learn a little something.
有什么不好吗
What's wrong with that?
没有 没有
Nothing. Nothing.
嘿 你是只小器龙
Hey, you're a cheapasaurus!
开玩笑的啦 谢了 感激不尽
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Thank you. I'm very grateful.
嘿 摩妮卡 这是什么
Hey, Mon, what is this?
噢
Oh!
我中学时的泳衣
That's my bathing suit from high school.
我当年比较肿
I was a little bigger then.
我还以为 这是康涅狄格州的遮雨布
Oh, I thought that's what they used to cover Connecticut when it rains.
摩妮卡 这带子里录的是什么
Hey, what's on this videotape?
我不晓得 放进去看看
Hey, you got me, put it in.
嗨      嘿
Hi.         Hey.
照这边 杰克 好
Over here, Jack. Okay.
瑞秋就要进门了
I see, Rachel's coming up the path.
她是不是很美 杰克你能拍到吗
Doesn't she look pretty? Jack? Can you get this?
我的天
Oh my God!
你的鼻子怎么了
What is with your nose?
医生不得不给我做缩鼻术 因为我鼻中隔偏曲
They had to reduce it because of, of my deviated septum.
好吧 我错了
Okay, I was wrong.
这才是康涅狄格州的遮雨布
That's what they use to cover Connecticut.
知道这是什么吗
You know what this is?
这是我们准备要去毕业舞会的录像
This is us getting ready for the prom.
我们不要看这个
You know what, you guys, we don't have to watch this
要 要看
Oh yeah we do.
要啦      很好玩的
Come on.         It's fun!
来拍摩妮卡
Get a shot of Monica.
摩妮卡人呢      在这边 爸
Where's Monica?         Over here, Dad!
等等 镜头怎么伸缩
Wait. How do you zoom out?
在这儿呢
There she is!
有个女孩把摩妮卡吞掉了
Some girl ate Monica!
闭嘴 人上镜会显得胖十磅
Shut up! The camera adds ten pounds.
那到底有多少镜头对着你
So how many cameras are actually on you?
哦 你看起来好棒
Oh, you look so great!
你也是 真漂亮
So do you! You look beautiful!
糟了     干嘛
Oops.       What?
我的蛋黄酱沾到你身上了
Shoot, I think I got mayonaise on you.
没关系 只是肩膀 没沾到衣服
Oh, that's okay, it's just the shoulder, it's not my dress.
大家笑一笑
Everybody smile!
噢      老爸 关掉
Oh!        Dad, turn it off!
就是关的
It's off.
哪有 红灯还亮着
Dad, it is not! What's with the red light?
那就表示关了 对吧 罗斯
It's the off light. Right, Ross?
很帅嘛
Looking good, Mr. Cotter.
你今晚看起来很美      哦 谢了
You look pretty tonight.         Oh, thanks.
你这个暑假要做什么
So what are you gonna do this summer?
你知道的 待在家里 玩我的音乐
Oh, you know, I'm just gonna, I'm gonna hang out, work on my music.
我的扣子松了吗 这些东东一直往下掉
Is my hook unhooked? These things keep falling down.
我看看 我不晓得
Let me see. I don't know.
你打算如何
So, what are you gonna do...
男生们到了
Oh! The guys are here!
过暑假
this summer?
玩你的音乐
Work on your music?
我的天 是洛伊贾柏立克
Oh my God! Look, there's Roy Gublik!
洛伊看"星球大战"看了317遍
You know, Roy saw "Star Wars" 317 times.
还上过报纸
His name was in the paper.
奇普呢 他怎么还没到
Where's Chip? Why isn't he here yet?
他会来的 放心吧
He'll be here, okay? Take a chill pill.
好了
There.
我刚才是跟瑞秋说 洛伊碰了我的胸部
I just told Rachel that Roy touched my boob.
没有男伴 我去不成毕业舞会了
I can't go to my own prom without a date.
去不了了 来不及了
I can't! It's too late!
你不去的话 我也不想去
If you're not going then I don't want to go either.
我要宰了奇普
Oh, I'm gonna kick Chip's ass!
我有个好主意
I have a wonderful idea.
你应该带瑞秋去参加毕业舞会
You should take Rachel to the prom.
我很怀疑
Doubtful.
杰克 摄影机给我 你来跟你儿子说
Jack, give me that. Talk to your son.
好 赶快      这东西真重
All right, go on.         This thing's heavy.
你妈妈说的对 带她去 你可以穿我的礼服
Your mother's right. Take her. You can wear my tux.
她不会想跟我去的
Dad, she won't want to go with me.
她当然愿意 你是大学生了
Of course she would! You're a college man!
我不晓得      哦 好了啦
I don't know.         Well, come on.
你就不想试试看
Don't you wanna find out?
真不敢相信 我去不成自己的毕业舞会
I can't believe I don't get to go to my own prom!
这太残酷了
This is so harsh!
好 帮我拿键盘      好孩子 好孩子
Okay. Hold my board.         Attaboy! Attaboy!
我想我们也看够了 可以关掉了
Okay, you guys, ya know, I think we've seen enough, let's turn it off.
不要 别这样
No, no, no.
那好吧 我不看了
Okay, fine, well, I'm not gonna watch, alright?
快点 小鬼 咱们走
Come on, kid. Let's go!
哇 真是帅啊
My! Are you handsome!
给大家瞧瞧
Let's show them!
等一下 爸
Just a sec, Dad.
好 要酷 酷一点
Okay, be cool. Just be cool.
好了 爸
Okay, Dad.
瑞秋 准备好了没 你的白马王子来了
Rachel, ready or not, here comes your knight in shining.
哦 糟了
Oh no.
再见 不用等我们了
Bye! Don't wait up!
奇普
Chip!
哦 天哪
Oh, dear!
杰克 这个怎么关啊
Jack. How do I turn this off?
按下按钮      哪一个 哪个按钮 杰克
Press the button.        Which one? Which button? Jack!
那一个 就那一个
The button! The button!
真不敢相信你那么做了
I can't believe you did that.
是呀
Yeah. well
看到没 他是她的龙虾
See? He's her lobster!
跟他跳舞
Dance with him!
妈 我饿了
Mom, I'm hungry!
跟你爸爸跳舞
Dance with your father.
我或许不会跳什么闪舞啦
I don't know any of your flash dances.
不过我上了舞池 亦非等闲之辈
But I'm no slouch on the dance floor.
好吧
All right.
哦 杰克      哦 茱蒂
Oh, Jack!        Oh, Judy!
哦 茱蒂
Oh, Judy!
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧